/**
 * THIS IS SIMPLE TODO LIST
 * 
 * If you want to write here your own TODO items, please write it in appropriate
 * section under your nick.
 * If you want script some functionality (it means one or more TODO points)
 * whitch is not associated to you add your nick in bars before that item.
 * Do it only if this script will be pushed to repository in one of your next few
 * commits. You can create your own section in TODO list. TODO section is based
 * on project url (like root/wow/ or root/account/ or / [/ simple means root]).
 * 
 * Section / means page loaded immediately after visit site and all common
 * functionalities like top navigation bar(login, create acc, account, explore...),
 * footer, and all other common places.
 * NOTE: it means places that have same functionality from user's perspective,
 * same functionality on server side script is not condition. 
**/

<section>/
<!-- AndzinSan -->
  * locale selector on bottom of page
  * full site search
  * autologin by "Keep me logged in" checkbox
  * login by name or email
  * update section "My Games" on main pege after login for view registered game
    accounts associated to webcs account with their names, not expansion name
</section>

<section>account/management
<!-- AndzinSan -->
  * add more account details (account id, email, registration date,
    last login date) under ACCOUNT DETAILS section
  * set details about associated game accounts (gmlevel, join date, last ip,
    last login, status locked and online, mutetime and expansion by image)
  
  <section>account/management/add-game
  <!-- AndzinSan -->
    * redirect this link to new game accoount creation: account/creation/wow/signup/
      with same functionality but better design and organization    
  </section>
  <section>account/management/settings/change-email
  <!-- AndzinSan -->
    * make it fully functional  
  </section>
  <section>account/management/settings/change-password
  <!-- AndzinSan -->
    * make it fully functional  
  </section>
  <section>account/management/wow-account-conversion
  <!-- AndzinSan -->
    * make it fully functional in 3 steps for associate unassociated game
      accounts with webcs account    
  </section>
</section>

<section>account/support/password-reset
                        /password-reset-select
                        /password-reset-secred-answer
                        /password-reset-success
<!-- AndzinSan -->
  * add texts to en localization
</section>


